Vanna Chhil

Newmarket, ON I9n 0r7 vannachhil5_bah@indeedemail.com 905 392 0493

Skilled welder with proficiency in MIG, stick welding, drill press, crane operation, and metal fabrication. Specialise in using torch, plasma, air sac and forklifts. Capable of reading, and interpreting blueprint, drawing, diagrams.

Work Experience

Fabrication Welder

Terradyne Armored Vehicles - Newmarket, ON July 2015 to October 2018

Build vehicles, grind, using measure, wiring vehicles. Make custom parts for customer's need

Robotic Welder/Fabrication welder

3D Storage Systems - Newmarket, ON March 2014 to July 2015

Assisted machine operators with finished parts.

Fabricated large and small parts per drawing and assembled parts as required

Press Operator/welder

Dynamic Suspensions - Newmarket, ON January 2011 to March 2014

Adjusted alignment, drill, cutter dies, and holding devices.

Assisted machine operators with finished pieces

Oversaw the production process and managed the production schedule

Tested products or sub-assemblies for functionality or quality

Education

High school Diploma

Huron heights Secondary school - Newmarket, ON

Skills

- Blueprint Reading, forklift driver, solvent bonding ability, extremely quick leaner, expert welder, exceptional organizational skills
- Welder Fabricator
- Fabrication
- MIG
- Welding

• Body Shop